Privacy Policy
==============

**Email:** [\[email protected\]](https://www.ekoru.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Physical Address:** C507 Phileo Damansara 1, Kuala Lumpur Malaysia

User-Centric Data Handling
--------------------------

Ekoru is deeply committed to safeguarding user privacy. In our unwavering commitment to privacy, we assure you that no personal information is collected or stored. The extension operates exclusively on your device to block intrusive ads, respecting your privacy at every step.

Anonymous Statistics for Enhancement
------------------------------------

In our pursuit of continuous improvement, Ekoru may collect anonymous usage statistics. These statistics, devoid of any personally identifiable information, are instrumental in refining the extension's performance and enhancing overall user satisfaction.

Commitment to No User Tracking
------------------------------

Your online activities remain shielded from scrutiny. Ekoru refrains from engaging in user profiling, ensuring that your digital footprint stays private and secure.

Localized Storage Optimization
------------------------------

For improved efficacy, Ekoru may leverage local storage on your device. This storage is restricted to essential data required for the extension's functionality and is never shared or transmitted.

Dynamic Adaptation through Regular Updates
------------------------------------------

To stay ahead of the dynamic landscape of online advertising, Ekoru releases periodic updates. These updates are geared towards enhancing performance and ensuring compatibility with a diverse range of websites.

Limited Communication with Servers
----------------------------------

Ekoru upholds transparency in its operations. The extension refrains from unnecessary communication with external servers unless imperative for updates. Any data exchanged during updates is confined to what is essential for maintaining the latest version.

Installation Implies Consent
----------------------------

By choosing to install Ekoru, you implicitly consent to the terms articulated in this privacy policy.

Accessible Support and Communication
------------------------------------

For any queries or apprehensions regarding the privacy policy or the Ekoru extension, please reach out to us at **[\[email protected\]](https://www.ekoru.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**. We are here to address your concerns, provide clarity and ensure your peace of mind in navigating the digital realm.

Save our oceans. Every search on Ekoru raises funds to keep our oceans and marine life healthy.

##### Useful links

##### Follow us

By installing the Ekoru browser new tab extension, I accept and agree to the [Ekoru Privacy](https://www.ekoru.org/privacy/) and [Terms of Service](https://www.ekoru.org/terms/).
